Tomislav Balabanov

Web Designer at Freelancer.com

tomislav.balabanov@hotmail.com

Summary

I'm currently studying at Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering in Skopje, Macedonia. Department of application of E-technologies,

Applied E-technologies.

My range of design services include creating design for new websites or improving existing ones. I have worked with clients like: Moda Calzini, Beatrix Crew, E-Medikal etc.

I will work with you to discover what you need and create the best solution. My priorities are quality and respect of deadlines and budget. I love to share my enthusiasm and passion for design, so feel free to contact me and let's get the conversation started.

Experience

Web Developer at Fiverr

September 2016 - Present (2 months)

Web Designer at Freelancer.com

October 2015 - Present (1 year 1 month)

Web Designer at Beatrix Crew

August 2016 - Present (3 months)

My main part of work consists of Web Designing their website, Managing their Social media and all the IT related needs of the company.

Insurance and finance agent at WVP Group

2015 - Present (1 year)

My work is consisted of insurance, finance consulting and team work. Which gives a never ending career.

General Manager at Irish Pub Balaban's

July 2016 - August 2016 (2 months)

To monitor the Stuff.

Web Designer at Moda Calzini

March 2010 - August 2014 (4 years 6 months)

I have a responsibilities for creating the website and menaging social networks.

Founder at HarsoftHC

October 2008 - January 2010 (1 year 4 months)

I founded HarsoftHC as a hobby first, then it growth to a business. Then i ask a friend to help me so we can accomplish more.

Services that we offered:

- -Formating Computers
- -Reinstall OS
- -Web Design
- -Computer Network Architecture
- -Advice for: backing up files, system problems, errors, connection problems.

Projects

Beatrix Dance League Website

September 2016 to Present

Members: Tomislav Balabanov, Emir Al Kafadji

My portfolio website

October 2016 to Present

Members:Tomislav Balabanov

I decided that I need my own portfolio website, so I created one so people can find and contact me easier.

Education

Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Skopje Macedonia

Engineer in Computer Science and Engineering, Department of application of E-technologies, Applied E-

Technologies, 2015 - 2018

Grade: 2

Saba, Skopje Macedonia

MIddle-school, Computer and Information Sciences, General, 2012 - 2015

Publications

A Quick Overview of Hashcat and oclHashcat

Tomislav Balabanov August 11, 2016

Authors: Tomislav Balabanov

A quick overview for hashcat and oclhashcat

Remove Users From Your Network Using Airmon-ng

Tomislav Balabanov August 30, 2016

Authors: Tomislav Balabanov

Certifications

Microsoft 6425C: Configuring And Troubleshooting Windows Server 2008, Active Directory Domain Services

Semos Education

Microsoft 6292: Installing and Configuring Windows Client

Semos Education

Web Design

Semos Education

Penetration Testing and Ethical Hacking

Cybrary License C-27bd72311-a2f5b1 July 2016

CompTIA Security+

Cybrary License C-27bd72311-f861b0 July 2016

Cryptography

Cybrary License C-27bd72311-413d9a3 July 2016

Social Engineering and Manipulation

Cybrary License C-27bd72311-2ed9ba August 2016

Computer and Hacking Forensics

Cybrary License C-27bd72311-8a34401 August 2016

Responsive Design with Dreamweaver CS6

Lynda.com License BD4230E6181C4FD8903D072B1D65DC54 September 2016

Ethical Hacking: Session Hijacking

Lynda.com License 42AEB10BFB6D4F3482A143A82C294B37 September 2016

Foundations of IT Security: Core Concepts

Lynda.com License A7DB50 September 2016 to September 2016

Foundations of Cybersecurity

Lynda.com License A57623 September 2016 to September 2016

Foundations of IT Security: Operating System Security

Lynda.com License D9706A September 2016 to September 2016

Foundations of IT Security: Network Security

Lynda.com License 0C5C46 September 2016 to September 2016

Practical Cybersecurity

Lynda.com License B8B279 September 2016 to September 2016

IT Security Fundamentals

Lynda.com License BF627C September 2016 to September 2016

Understanding Secure Sockets Layer

Lynda.com License 999F8A September 2016 to September 2016

Cybersecurity with Cloud Computing

Lynda.com License 94B30D September 2016 to September 2016

Computer Forensics Essential Training

Lynda.com License 43E7B5 September 2016 to September 2016

Essentials of Cryptography and Network Security

Lynda.com License FC4BEF September 2016 to September 2016

Computer Security: Investigation and Response

Lynda.com License 90EC53 September 2016 to September 2016

Become an IT Security Specialist

Lynda.com September 2016 to September 2016

Preparing for the CompTIA Security+ Exam (SY0-401)

Lynda.com License 4584DA September 2016

Become a CompTIA Security+ Certified Security Professional

Lynda.com September 2016 to September 2016

Courses

Engineer in Computer Science and Engineering, Department of application of E-technologies, Applied E-Technologies

Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering, Skopje

Macedonia

11
12
1
2
3
4
5
6
7
8
9
10

Skills & Expertise

Computer Security

Web Development

Web Design

C++

 \mathbf{C}

Network Security

Information Security

Adobe Photoshop

Networking

Network Administration

Music Production

Guitar Playing

Acoustic Guitar

Electric Guitar

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

HTML

HTML5

Operating Systems

Kali Linux

Arch Linux

Microsoft Office

Microsoft Excel

Microsoft Word

Microsoft Outlook

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Social Media Optimization (SMO)

Teamwork

Social Media

Team Leadership

PHP

Strategic Planning

Insurance

Life Insurance

Negotiation

Sales Management

Sales

Health Insurance

Communication

Research

Volunteer Experience

Creating elements for their show "Pieces". at Beatrix Crew

May 2016 - Present

I was making elements for their show, wood elements with led lights on them. My main work was to create the wood elements and then attach led lights to them.

Languages

English

Macedonian

Serbian

Interests

Technologies, investing, music, guitar, design, IT seucirty.

Tomislav Balabanov

Web Designer at Freelancer.com

tomislay.balabanoy@hotmail.com



2 person has recommended Tomislav

"Tomislav is an ambitious developer, who is eager to learn new things, explore new fields and will work hard to get things done. Working with Tomislav on the website for Beatrix Crew was great because he is always willing to listen and learn, while paying attention to details when designing a website. I highly recommend him to any company that wants an up-and-coming web designer."

— Emir Al Kafadji, Marketing Manager, Beatrix Crew, managed Tomislav at Beatrix Crew

"Tomislav is one of those people you would always want to work with. He did an excellent job by creating our Beatrix Dance League Project's web-site. He works fast and he is devoted to his job. He completed all of our requests without any problems, and his work met our goals overall. Tomislav is a hard-working enthusiast and always open for cooperation."

— Ivana Balabanova, Owner, Beatrix Crew, was Tomislav's client

Contact Tomislav on LinkedIn